Hello Hello
Здравствуйте
How is your Khmelnitsky Ukraine
Здравствуйте Как ваш Хмельницкий Украина
where are you from such a jaunty
Вы откуда такая бодренькая
oh with the same non-rubber city that you
ой с той самой не резиновый которую вы
don’t like the
не любите
city which there are many cities of this non-
город какой там много городов этой не
rubber non-rubber
резиновой не резиновая
understood yes And how do you
понял да А как вы в этой не резиновой
feel about the fact that Russia attacked
относитесь к тому что Россия напала на
Ukraine in this non-rubber
Украину
to the fact that
я плохо отношусь к тому что
This is an attack But I think that this is not an
Это нападение Но я считаю что не
attack But that this is
нападение А что это
protection, that is, for protection, they
это защита то есть для защиты
kill people in Ukraine, look,
убивают людей в Украине вот смотрите
let's talk
будем общаться
[music]
[музыка]
you threaten me and then I Well, what will I do,
вы мне угрожаете и тут я Ну что я сделаю
I probably just rudely speaking
я наверное просто-напросто грубо говоря
there  I'm sorry I'm going to say a thing now I'll give
там я я прошу прощения Я сейчас вещь
you a smack in the face
скажу дам вам по морде
Tell me now I'll piss off I tensed
скажите Сейчас отпиздим Я напрягся
like Ukraine how Ukraine threatened Russia
как Украина как Украина угрожала России
who will otpizdit Tell me how Ukraine
кто кого отпиздит Расскажите как Украина
threatened Russia interesting
угрожал России интересно
by what it placed on TO on its
тем что размещала на ТО на своей
territory
территории
where it should have been placed
где надо было размещено
when Turkey placed its Turkey
когда Турция разместила свои Турции
look  we are Ukraine, for example, Lithuania
смотрите мы Украины Вот например Литва
Latvia Estonia joined NATO
Латвия Эстония вошли НАТО
Finland joined NATO
Финляндия вошла в НАТО шла
Ukraine went even if it wanted to
Украина даже если бы она хотела причем
where does Russia threaten to lift it
тут России что угрожаем на подъемного
captured that flight that
захватила что полет что полет
flight of a rocket so the flight of a rocket from
полет ракеты так полет ракеты от
Finland is closer to Moscow And
Финляндии ближе к Москве И
St. Petersburg is not my propaganda
санкт-петербургу это не моя пропаганда
the military told me this I open the
это мне военные рассказывали Я открываю
map
карту
while you open the map No right now
при вас открываю карту Нет прямо сейчас
I’ll tell you
вот расскажу
roughly speaking there for
грубо говоря еще там вот
13 years you’ve
13 год у вас там
been jumping there who doesn’t jump he is a Muscovite we have a
скачут кто не скачет он москаль у нас
completely different thing here and
совершенно другая вот вещь и
I explain to explain there is air defense
объясняю объяснить есть ПВО
if let’s say people That’s exactly the North
вот если допустим люди Вот именно Север
some air defenses are flying there, they are
летит там одни ПВО стоят
from Ukraine, they are completely different
от Украины стоят совершенно другие
That’s it,
Вот именно
you attacked, you are
вы напали смотрите вы
watching Putin I just remember that Putin
смотрите Путин Я просто помню что Путин
said that the goal for Ukraine is
сказал что цель для Украины
dementalization, he won’t say a word the
дементализация он ни слова не скажет
goal is for Ukraine not to join NATO,
цель чтобы Украина не вступала в НАТО
you think that this is not so I
вы думаете что это вот это не так Я
I think it’s not so
думаю это не так
Okay, in short, he wants to capture everything
Ладно он короче хочет захватить все
else, he
остальное
captured the part of
захватил часть
Kherson, Crimea, Donetsk
Херсонская еще Крым Донецк
Well, let’s say they
Ну допустим
themselves want
сами хотят
an accountant
бухгалтер
I somehow thought we somehow had
Я как-то думал у нас как-то в Украине
more elegant accountants in Ukraine
бухгалтера более элегантные
state-owned
на государственном предприятии
accounting company at a private one
бухгалтерии на частном
No, I’m on my own, that is, an accountant for
Нет я сама по себе то есть бухгалтер на
different films, yes, it’s
разные фильмы да типа обслужить
more profitable to serve it I agree, work at home
так выгоднее Я согласен дома работаете
somewhere from home, that is, don’t go out at home,
где-то из дома то есть дома не выходите
so it’s
так дома
not always interesting
не всегда интересно
and important for
и важно потому что
you, because it’s important to you how often you play roulette  they say
вам важно как часто вам рулетке говорят
that you are a fool that you are finished for example
что вы дура что вы конченые например
But I think that this is stupid Well, as you
Но я считаю что это глупо Ну как вы
said, it is important to hear people's opinions people
сказали важно мнение людей услышать люди
say you are finished Archie ha for example you are finished
говорят вы конченые Арчи ха например вы
they want some kind of anger at
Это просто хотят какую-то злость на
the Russians, the
россиян
invaders are
захватчики же
absolutely not an invader, I
абсолютно не захватчик у меня
have a man, yes
у вас мужчина есть да
[music]
[музыка]
I don’t even know in
Я даже не знаю
10 years, probably the
лет через 10 наверное
poor fellow And who does he work,
бедолажка А кем он работает
oh he
ой
drove,
водила
he drove, that is, the truck driver is
он Водила то есть Дальнобойщик
such
таким
heavy trucks And where is he
большегрузы А где он сейчас
at work now
на работе
actually, I have been able to amuse my work for a long time
вообще-то Я уже давно свою работу
Well, yes,
Ну да прикольно
such a cool question
такой вопрос
What happened they
Что случилось
killed and loved
перебили и любили
And I don’t like it when they beat Well, no one
А я не люблю когда бьют Ну никто не
likes food, but what are you now
любит чтобы еда а вот то что вы сейчас
let’s say How are
допустим Как вы
you Patriot almost I understand
вот вы Patriot почти я правильно понимаю
something correctly  what are you saying now that Russia
что то что вы сейчас говорите что Россия
didn’t attack Ukraine something didn’t
не нападала на Украине что-то не
attack the results that you were
нападение результатов что вас были
somewhere on the head there are some
где-то по голове там какие-то
thought processes now that
мыслительные процессы теперь плохо
cognitive functions do not work well
работают когнитивные функции
like For example, you can somehow help you
как Например можно как-то помочь вам
fix it so that you can
исправить чтобы
recover to then later
восстановились до чтобы потом уже
normally thought they didn’t support
нормально думали не поддерживали
me, it will help me a lot,
мне очень поможет есть
I’m on my own island,
я на собственном острове
it’s in the Seychelles region, it’s
это в районе сейшел
just two, well, well, lie your head there,
просто-напросто вот ну лежать голову там
touch it Probably it will help
трогать Наверное это поможет
you can help
вы сможете помочь
or a Ukrainian somewhere in the Kherson region
или украинец где-то в Херсонской области
can lie down for two years there is such a
можете полежать года два есть такая
program
программа
oh no there  somehow the earth is heavy, very
ой нет там как-то земля тяжеловато очень
heavy. Yes, it’s scorched, maybe there
тяжелая Да еще этом выжженная может быть
are guys who can organize
есть ребята которые могут организовать
for you.
вам Если уж лежать то я вот там
when it is necessary to restore it
Она когда надо восстанавливать ее
Obviously not due to the fact that when I lie down
Явно не за счет того что когда я лягу
there in this land it’s right
там в эту землю правильно
in England Yes, but why
в Англии Да а почему
because the British know how to work and the
потому что англичане умеют работать а
Russians don’t know how to work No, this is not the point of a
русские не умеют работать Нет дело не в
completely different mentality and
совершенно другой менталитет и
management
управление
of the manager there are certain things By the way,
управляшки есть определенные вещи Кстати
you have  it’s also not
у вас тоже этого нету
what specifically, in Russia it’s worse than
чем конкретно вот в России хуже чем
management than in England, you can say
управление чем в Англии можете сказать
an example
пример
honestly,
честно
Russians are more stupid in terms of the fact that
русские более тупые в плане того что
where they need cunning, they are direct.
где надо хитростью они прямые
This is stupidity.
Это тупость Я считаю
it’s not the turn of the Russians’ benefit Unfortunately, the
русских это нету К сожалению
Russians are more stupid than others Yes,
русские более тупые чем другие Да
no, you are now
нет вы сейчас
Russians, they are stupid about the fact that Russians
русские они тупые о том что русские по
are much simpler than English slimes,
сравнению с англичанами слаймами они
they don’t, well, it won’t work, let’s say the
у них не ну не получится допустим у
Russians make McDonald’s, well, for example
русских сделать МакДональдс ну к примеру
Well, because because  so I say the
Ну потому что потому что вот я говорю
mentality is different Why the Russians can
менталитет другой Почему русские могут
make, for example, a balalaika they can
сделать например балалайку они могут
make McDonald's exactly a balalaika they
сделать МакДональдс именно балалайку они
can do
могут сделать
[music]
[музыка]
completely different things
совершенно разные вещи
That's why What is called Spain
Вот почему Что называется Испания
which was
которая была
the Lord of the Seas lost is called England
Владыка морей проиграл называется Англии
so Why and because there is more So
так Почему и потому что там более Вот
then they did not realize  how
они тогда не сообразили как надо
some were
какие-то были
orthodox,
ортодок
let's just now I'm just
давайте сейчас просто
wondering, it's not about history Here you are
мне интересно вот не про историю Вот вы
as an accountant about the dollar here Let's
как бухгалтер про доллар вот Давайте
continue You saw that the dollar is already
продолжим Вот вы видели что доллар уже
a hundred rubles Yes a hundred rubles Here's how
сотка Да сотка рублей Вот вы как
an accountant will say it is good
бухгалтер скажет это для России хорошо
or bad for Russia That the dollar has become
или плохо Что доллар стал
relatively  regarding what,
относительно относительно что
regarding some things there Well, that
относительно там каких-то вещей Ну то
is, the fact is that most
есть Дело в том что у нас большинство
people here do not hold
людей не держат
Well, in short, as it were,
Ну короче как бы
but for you personally it is good or bad
а для вас лично это хорошо или плохо
relatively
относительно
better for the dollar to rise or
лучше чтобы доллар поднимался или никак
not better,
не лучше
I say again I was scared,
я еще раз говорю я пугался
you see  what an ass because of the dollar Yes,
вы видите какая [__] из-за доллара Да
I know that it’s not in dollars
я знаю что не в долларах
Well, in principle, it’s very good to keep in
Ну в принципе очень неплохо держать в
yens in yens you personally keep your
иенах в иенах вы лично держите свои
movements in your genes and stably Yes you
движения в генах и стабильно Да вы венах
keep your savings in your veins of course I understand
держите свои сбережения конечно понял вы
where you keep it Cool and good, but you
где на держите Прикольно да хорошо а вот
can  explain What is fraught with for Russians
можете объяснить Чем чревато для россиян
the rise in the dollar exchange rate because many
поднятие курса доллара потому что многие
do not understand that
не понимают думают что
I mean, you just go to the store and you can
В смысле просто магазин заходишь и вот
see it is growing
но видно растут таки да
[laughter]
[смех]
and honestly
и честно
I’m also interested in how
мне вот тоже интересно как вас
the ruble is falling
рубль падает
[music]
[музыка]
Utilities We have a problem now  Housing and communal services We have had
ЖКХ У нас сейчас проблема Не ЖКХ У нас у
22 years old, look at us again we have a
нас 22 год смотрите у нас еще раз у нас
problem Not housing and communal services we have a problem morons from
проблема Не ЖКХ у нас проблема [__] из
Russia who climb on our Earth This is the
России которые лезут на нашу Землю Вот
main article, let's have our
это основная статья давайте
main cost item, this is
у нас основная статья затрат это она
all these [ __ ] climb and we spend a
все эти долбоебы лезут и мы тратим очень
lot of money  in order to kill them
много денег для того чтобы их убить
quickly kill that
побыстрее убить
is,
То есть
if this problem goes away, then you have that
если вот эта проблема уйдет то у вас что
paradise will come, we will begin to return to paradise,
рай наступит начнем возвращаться в рай
yes,
да
because while this garbage exists Yes, it
потому что пока эта [__] есть Да она
was us, look if we are watching Yes, why
был смотрите если мы смотрим Да почему
your paradise was still explaining, see explaining
ваш рай был еще объясняю смотри объясняю
more  once
еще раз
in Ukraine Here you are as an accountant yes you have
в Украине Вот вы как бухгалтер да у вас
this minimum wage the minimum wage
этот МРОТ минимальный размер оплаты
in Ukraine even after
труда в Украине даже после того как
Russia attacked in the fourteenth year
Россия в четырнадцатом году напала Да
in Ukraine the level of the minimum
в Украине уровень минимальный уровень
wage was higher than in Russia
оплаты труда был выше чем в России
the level of the minimum wage
уровень минимальный уровень платы труда
was higher than in Russia Why
был выше чем на России Почему
I ask again why
я еще раз спрашиваю почему
because in Russia Russia in the Urals in
потому что на России Россия на Урале на
Russia I
России
ask again why what are the
еще раз спрашиваю почему это какие
laws of the Ukrainian language Yes the law of the
законы украинского языка Да закон
Ukrainian language  they say So we
украинского языка говорят Значит у нас
have adopted the spelling of the first Moscow
приняли правописание первое Москва
write with a small letter grow here
писать с маленькой буквы расти вот
Russia write Zelensky
Россия писать Зеленский
Zelensky
Зеленский
write words Yes with a small letter Moscow
слова писать Да с маленькой буквы Москва
write with a small letter in Russia This
с маленькой буквы писать на России Вот
is not a Russian to speak We are forbidden
и не россияна говорить У нас запрещено
a fine from if I speak Russians
штраф от если я буду говорить россияне
this will be a fine  administrative
это штраф будет административная
responsibility is
ответственность
only called Orcs
только Орки называем
Yes, there is, and if they say finished Orcs, they
Да еще есть а если говорят конченые Орки
even pay the state extra How many
то даже доплачивают государство Сколько
dollars, let
долларов давайте
me be finished,
я буду [__]
and how about money or phrase by
а он как по деньгам или по фразе по
phrase, you need to tell people up to 100 times in a month,
фраза надо за месяц до 100 раз сказать
and that is, one person one phrase
а то есть один человек одна фраза Так
So  I have just 100 today, so
вот вы у меня как раз 100 сегодня так
I already said Listen, I’m really glad
что я уже сказал Слушайте я прям рада
that you have earned, I understand yes Do you
что вы заработали понял да Как вы
think you live richly by Russian standards
считаете вы вот по российским меркам
No, I just heard that in Russia
Нет просто я услышал такое что в России
there are no toilet refrigerators this is true
нет этих холодильника унитаза это правда
Yes you know here I am  I don’t know what
Да вы знаете вот я не знаю что это у
I have here, let’s
меня вот тут стоит
tell us now whether
нам говорят
it’s a mock-up or it really drains You can
это макет или он реально сливает Можете
turn it on, it drains
включить он сливает
it works
он работает
Well, the brown stripe is from rust
Ну полоса коричневая такая от ржавчины
or what do
или что
you imagine find that I have
вы представляете найти что у меня есть
a bath Show the bath Show yourself in the
ванна Покажите ванну Покажите себя в
wolf’s bath Come on  Show it to you, it’s also
волка А ну Покажите именно вам она тоже
brown Yes, it’s also brown
коричневая да тоже коричневая
I don’t know
Я не знаю
brown Rust
коричневая Ржавчина
the sink
раковина прикиньте
think it’s such a design I think that the military will come soon and
Я думаю что скоро приедет военные
take it away
заберут
well
ну
Turn on the water the
Включите это воду
sink
а ту белую раковицу Вани вы показывали
itself
господи Сейчас дойду
here I go there I have a small house
тут там хожу У меня же маленький домик
to walk
ходить
it’s Moscow or the Moscow region  it’s
это у вас Москва или Московская область
just that
у нас просто напросто
no one sells what kind of domesto in what it
никто не продает какой domesto в чем
says you
говорит у вас
have left on February 22 All this is your private courtyard
22 февраля ушел Все это вас дворик
No of course you can show the view from the window
Нет конечно можете показать вид из окна
Show the view
Покажите вид
Lord Moscow Moscow It’s
Господи Московская Москва
cool and the products What kind of food do you have in
Прикольно а продукты Какие у вас
the refrigerator
холодильнике
what else
что еще
cat pans of course it’s
кастрюли кошачья конечно
so
вот так
cool here at least more  less normal
прикольно тут хоть более менее нормально
or you can show it like a cat I have never
а можете показать это кошачью Я никогда
seen a cat walking in a pot where
не видел как кошачью иду в кастрюле где
Well what is it Well they
Ну что это такое
cook porridge for cats dogs it’s
Ну кашу варят для котов собак
hard to see it’s cat food she
плохо видно еще это кошачья еда она
understood it costs a bowl
понял она это миска стоит
Cool And how many cats do you have
Прикольно А сколько у вас котов
I have cats  no, they are there in the
у меня у меня кошек нету они там во
yard there are
дворе
8 cats,
там 8 кошек
not one. A cat came and gave birth, then the second one,
не одна Пришла кошка родила потом вторая
someone ran away, someone No, I know
кто-то разбежался кто-то Нет я знаете
three residential ones. Can you show us the
три жилых А можете показать на
layout of what, let's say
планировка какая
we already say it normally, I
давайте мы уже так нормально говорим я
meet a normal person in a cage, then
нормального человека встретите клетке то
Usually when drunken cattle  I'm wondering
Обычно когда пьяное [__] мне интересно
I never imagined Muscovites
я никогда не представлял себе москвичей
how they live here you really made me
как они живут вот вы реально мне сделали
this collection can you tell me about what
эту коллекцию можете про какие
layouts Muscovites have How the furniture is
планировки у москвичей Как там мебель
arranged there
расставлена
I saw I was abroad in Moscow I
вот я видел я был за границей в Москве
wasn't interested
не был мне интересно
[music]
[музыка]
is that
это что
Yes it's ok here
Да тут нормально нормально
[music]
[музыка]
so, well, twist it in the bedroom Yes, let's see it
так ну покрутите в спальне Да посмотрим
like this and the norm is a fan there are curtains Well, it's
так а норма вентилятор есть шторы Ну
normal usually Moscow such a
нормально обычно Московская такая
bedroom Yes, there you have a trillash there by
спальня Да вот вас там есть трильяш у
a bunch of mirrors Super cool That is, you
кучей зеркал Супер классно То есть вы
can dance in front of them there,
там перед ними танцевать можете там
for example, you dance with your husband,
например с мужем танцуете
but this is already
но это уже
a  here a little bit here Because my daughter is
а тут здесь чуть-чуть Потому что дочка
sleeping
спит
little little ones
маленькие маленькие
we go out like a person
выходим Как человек
No there through God Oh
Нет там через Господи
this is a yard it turns out your private
О это дворик это получается ваш частный
yard Yes there is a dog in the yard for example there
двор Да есть собака во дворе например
is no cat the garage said
какая-то нет кошки гараж сказал гараж
there is a garage as you drive into the
есть как вы заезжаете в
yard there is no car over there  well,
дворжа нету машина вон там ставится Ну
where Show me how far to go from the car
где Покажи как далеко идти от машины
a little
немножко
hard to see you can look at these bushes
плохо видно можете к этим кустам
like a panorama of the yard I want to
посмотрел как двор панорама Я хочу
see the house from the side of the yard like this
увидеть дом со стороны двора вот так Ой
I say,
на самом деле я говорю
well,
ну
they have 30 percent,
процентов 30 имеют
and look at your street, here is an asphalted street,
а улица смотрите у вас вот улица
and I get a second house from the street
а у меня получается второй дом от улицы
that is asphalted But the house is,
которая асфальтированная А вот дом есть
Lord, such pebbles that are
Господи такие камушки которые
rammed
утрамбованы
Well, how to get there As they say 30 meters,
Ну как проехать Как говорится 30 метров
I really didn’t see a friend of stones
я реально не видел другу из камней
with you already like that  well, we are like kindred spirits
с вами уже так хорошо мы Как родные души
for me stones just show me I will be
ради меня камни просто покажите я буду
satisfied I wo
удовлетворен
n’t come to me
не пойду ко мне
I already said
Я уже сказал
oh
ой
please hammer in the
забейте пожалуйста в
settlement Kiev work settlement
поселение Киевский рабочий поселок
Kievsky SNT Niva 2
Киевский СНТ Нива 2
everything is
все все
in Google maps there I know I myself
в Google картах там есть я знаю я сама
looked there by chance there is no
смотрела там случайно нет никакой
airfield to  I accidentally didn’t see what
аэродрома чтобы я случайно не видел что
your airfield is like, there’s no one nearby. It’s a little
такое у вас аэродрома нету рядом Он чуть
higher, the military say
выше военные говорят
Vnukovo is
Внуково
far from you
далеко от вас
regarding I
относительно
knew that
Я знала что
I’m sorry, such garbage will come.
я извиняюсь наступит такая [__]
I bought
я покупала
[laugh]
[смех]
because it’s straight full.
потому что это прям полная
it's just some kind of tinny yes
это же бред Это просто жесть какой-то да
really
действительно
just a question like this Guys and who are you
просто вопрос такие Ребята а вы от кого
defending from whom Yes
кого защищаете Да
Moscow
Москву
I also say
я тоже говорю
First of all the question of the guys [ __ ]
В первую очередь вопрос ребят [__]
Well they have already come to terms with the fact that
Ладно там уже смирились с тем что
Belgorod is there
Белгородская там
Bryansk region
Брянская область
yes
да
we are laughing yes that is, it
мы ржем
turns out
да то есть получается
because  that, as I understand it, that there is
потому что как бы я понимаю что есть
at least
хотя бы
here Partially on the
вот Частично
cities of Ukraine,
на города Украины
it’s an ass there, by the way, we were told that
то это [__] там кстати у нас заявили что
this August 24, this is our
24 этого августа это на наш день
independence day, Moscow will bombard
независимости будет Москву засыпать
a drone.
беспилотника Так что лучше 24 августа
then it’s
куда-то
clear, in
Понятно
short, we need to stand with hoses to
короче нам надо это стоять со шлангами
flood the house on
заливать дом
August 24, the festive fireworks in Moscow are being prepared,
24 августа готовится Праздничный салют в
it’s horror
это же ужас
it’s horror It’s not we who started
это же ужас Это ведь не мы начали
here recently We periodically watch It’s
Тут недавно Мы периодически смотрим У
like I watch TV there I don’t
нас там как я телевизор смотреть Не
like
люблю
all the news I read on the Internet Husband  mine,
я все Новости читаю в интернете Муж мой
too, but he got hooked on this one
тоже но он подсел на вот эту вот
[music]
[музыка]
and in short, this one here he
и короче значит этот вот это вот он
listens listens
слушает слушает
then he asks me something I say
потом там у меня что-то спрашивает Я
Listen, I speak honestly, I say
говорю Слушай я говорю честно я говорю у
everything is so [ __ ] up with me that I don’t want to
меня так все заебало что я я не хочу
listen because  what I’m telling
слушать потому что говорю меня вот
you now I’ll tell you I think that how I
сейчас я вам скажу Я думаю что как я
say it’s interesting when the FSB will come for me
говорю интересно когда за мной приедет
[laughter]
[смех]
It’s simply interesting when
Интересно просто напросто когда
we are kidding about the fact that
прикалываемся мы по поводу того что
Germany will freeze tomorrow the day after tomorrow they
завтра замерзнет Германия послезавтра
will turn off gas to
отключат газ
France
Франции
And after tomorrow Poland
А после после завтра Польша
will attack Ukraine Well this  it's
нападет на Украину Ну это херь
just not interesting when
просто-напросто не интересно когда вот
this is
это вот
Propaganda propaganda but wow yes yes
Пропаганда пропаганды но
never a normal thinking
да Да никогда нормальные мыслящий
person no one believes in this
человек никто в это не верит
fine so I say my
прекрасно вот я говорю у меня моя
classmate she lives in Germany we
одноклассница она живет Германии мы с
talked to her We have another
ней разговаривали У нас есть еще одна
classmate who had  a house near
одноклассница у которой был дом под
Kiev when all this dick started As
Киевом когда вся эта хер началась Как
they say,
говорится
she fled to Germany because
она сбежала в Германию потому что
we were bombing about it, I say, well, I
мы об этом разговаривали я говорю ну
express my opinion and my
высказываю свое мнение и мне мои
classmates Lenka she says and Why they
одноклассницы Ленка она говорит и Почему
say that's how
говорят вот
you are, I'm not like me at the same time
так как ты я не как я в то же время
I
я
for Russia but
за Россию но
not
не
I am against Ukraine when it is Nazi I
Я против Украины когда она нацистская
would very much like to Yes, it’s not a question
очень хотела бы чтобы Да не вопрос
that it be its own independent and that’s
чтобы она была своей независимой и вот
it
это вот
and that the central authorities hear
и чтобы центральные власти услышали
some here Well, how to say the regions before
какие-то вот Ну как сказать регионы до
What demands of Russia attacked us
Какие требования России на нас напала
about something else I say  I think that if
про другое говорю я думаю что если бы
you internally decided all this,
вот вы внутренне вот это вот все решили
I think that it would be much better and
Я думаю что это было бы намного лучше и
if That's exactly what I found
если бы Вот именно что нашел
here, most of the Russians would support
здесь бы поддержала большая часть
in terms of the fact that Well, what the [ __ ] to
россиян в плане того что Ну какого хуя
get in there when they solve their own
туда влезать когда они сами решают свои
problems
проблемы
solve their own  problems Here's the thing,
решаете свои проблемы Вот чем дело
therefore, it turns out,
поэтому поэтому получается
on the one hand, Russia breaks in, on the other
с одной стороны влезает Россия с другой
hand, it breaks in, what do you think, now how will it
стороны влезает как думаете теперь чем
all end?
закончи тся это все
you mean who will
нет я думаю что нет вы имеете ввиду кто
capture whom not here How will it end here
кого захватит не вот Чем закончится вот
Russia sent troops what you see
Россия ввела войска на что вы видите
will run away from near Kiev how it will all
убежит как из-под Киева чем это все
end I think that this will last for a very long time And
закончится Я думаю что это очень долго
how it will end with
будет продолжаться А чем закончится
nothing there
ничем
is an option you will capture or you
есть вариант Вы захватите или вы там все
will all die there in Ukraine  or you will run away from
умрете в Украине или вы убежите из
Ukraine, I
Украины
say again,
еще раз говорю
I don’t
не я
personally, I didn’t capture anything from you,
Лично я ничего вас не захватывал никакую
they don’t know, they fly there to you I
они не знают они летят туда к вам Я
understand, I understand, I understand I accept
понимаю я понимаю я понимаю Я принимаю
my question about this
у меня у меня по этому поводу вопрос
Yes, I have them,
Да они у меня есть
but how are you  ask questions to your
а как вы задаете вопросы к своему
leadership
руководству
by voting, that is, you are waiting to ask
голосованием а то есть вы ждете задать
a question already at the elections Yes, not only
вопрос аж на выборах Да нет не только
you have now For a year and a half there are
у вас сейчас есть Уже полтора года есть
some questions to your leadership
какие-то вопросы к своему руководству
How do you ask them,
Как вы их задаете
in addition to this, I can ask a question through public services
помимо этого я могу через госуслуги
You ask through  public services
задать вопрос Вы задаете через госуслуги
honestly honestly Who did you ask which of the
честно честно Кому вы задавали кому из
management you asked through public services
руководства вы задавали через госуслуги
questions Sobyanin
вопросов собянину
supports
поддерживает
and what did you ask yourself
и что вы спросили у себя
asked Sobyanin when the
спросил у Собянина когда
subway will be for me, so
метро будет мне вот
you were worried about the war, something didn’t
вы переживали за войну что-то вас не
work out for you
устраиваться
That’s good Here is a year and a half you
не было Вот хорошо Вот полтора года вы
Find what
Найди что
close to the war there was nothing
близко войны не было ничего
at all not interested in You have
вообще не интересует У вас есть
accumulated questions but you can’t
накопились у вас вопросы но вы никак не
tell me questions have accumulated Well, like
скажете мне накопились вопросы Ну типа
we’re just Why do drones fly over
мы просто Почему беспилотники летают над
your house
вашим домом
I say again I don’t want to know anything
я еще раз говорю я не хочу ничего знать
because, as they say, from the fact that I
потому что как говорится от того что я
I’ll ask you A drone flies at your
задам Летит летит беспилотник у вас на
home Why don’t you write to the state services
дома Почему вы не напишите в госуслуги
Sobyanin where the [ __ ] air defense can fall
Собянин где ПВО [__] он сможет упасть
on your head, you know,
вам на голову понимаете
well, it will fall from the fact that I ask a question
да ну упадет от того что я задам вопрос
or not a
или нет
child,
ребенок
and for those questions you are asked
а по тем вопросам вас спрашивают
a drone, it will fall when from the
беспилотник он упадет когда
fact that  I'll ask
от того что я буду спрашивать
Let
Давайте
Putin be a good president,
Путин хороший президент
very good for Russians for you
очень неплохой для россиян для вас
Russians I'll clarify for you under Putin
россиян Уточняю для вас при Путине над
drones fly over you Yes, ruble 100 of
вами летают беспилотники Да рубль 100
the way, I began to live better
пути нам я стала жить лучше
That is, before Putin, your shell was
То есть у вас до Путина раковина была
completely red And now only
полностью рыжая А теперь частично только
I partially moved here a year  back and so they littered
я сюда переехала год назад и так засрали
the sink
раковину
Ok Let's So look
Хорошо Давайте Так смотрите
I
я
have to say goodbye I'll open the maps
вынужден попрощаться я открою карты
I'm a major of the security service of Ukraine
я Майор службы безопасности Украины
Thank you for saying the addresses
Спасибо что вы там говорили адреса
said
говорили
the distance from the airport
дальность от аэропорта
and we'll adjust ours well
и скорректируем наши хорошо
prefer to the
предпочтите на канал Поставьте лайк
channel  and I’ll be back, after all, 6 kilograms of us
светло пару н и вернусь ведь по 6 нами
right at a time, autumn, and the ass of the
килограмм прям за раз осень а попок
soul and more important YouTube, driving us
души и дуже важнева YouTube загоняя нас
through quarries into a shadow ban and more
через карьерки в теневый бан и дуже
bogged down, the video is not shown to people in
боготола видео не показывается людям в
private, information about
частном на показывается информация про
streams is shown in order to have a little operational
стримы для того чтобы мало оперативный
whistle, prefer it right at a time, but  ass
свисток предпочтите прям за раз а попок
there in a kilo about cream video
там в килограмме о Крим видео
information and we
информация и мы с вами
will show you
покажем вам
[music]
[музыка]